module.exports = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "According%20to%20the%20International%20System%20of%20Units%2C%20how%20many%20bytes%20are%20in%20a%20kilobyte%20of%20RAM%3F",
            "correct_answer": "1000",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "512",
                "1024",
                "500"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "When%20was%20the%20programming%20language%20%22C%23%22%20released%3F",
            "correct_answer": "2000",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1998",
                "1999",
                "2001"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The%20series%20of%20the%20Intel%20HD%20graphics%20generation%20succeeding%20that%20of%20the%205000%20and%206000%20series%20%28Broadwell%29%20is%20called%3A",
            "correct_answer": "HD%20Graphics%20500",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "HD%20Graphics%20700%20",
                "HD%20Graphics%20600",
                "HD%20Graphics%207000"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20given%20to%20Android%204.3%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Jelly%20Bean",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lollipop",
                "Nutella",
                "Froyo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "On%20Twitter%2C%20what%20was%20the%20original%20character%20limit%20for%20a%20Tweet%3F",
            "correct_answer": "140",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "120",
                "160",
                "100"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What%20does%20LTS%20stand%20for%20in%20the%20software%20market%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Long%20Term%20Support",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Long%20Taco%20Service",
                "Ludicrous%20Transfer%20Speed",
                "Ludicrous%20Turbo%20Speed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Dutch%20computer%20scientist%20Mark%20Overmars%20is%20known%20for%20creating%20which%20game%20development%20engine%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Game%20Maker",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Stencyl",
                "Construct",
                "Torque%202D"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The%20C%20programming%20language%20was%20created%20by%20this%20American%20computer%20scientist.%20",
            "correct_answer": "Dennis%20Ritchie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Tim%20Berners%20Lee",
                "al-Khw%C4%81rizm%C4%AB",
                "Willis%20Ware"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What%20is%20the%20codename%20of%20the%20eighth%20generation%20Intel%20Core%20micro-architecture%20launched%20in%20October%202017%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Coffee%20Lake",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sandy%20Bridge",
                "Skylake",
                "Broadwell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Lenovo%20acquired%20IBM%27s%20personal%20computer%20division%2C%20including%20the%20ThinkPad%20line%20of%20laptops%20and%20tablets%2C%20in%20what%20year%3F",
            "correct_answer": "2005",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1999",
                "2002",
                "2008"
            ]
        }
    ]
}